Hello, I'm Killian. I am awful at Smash Brothers, can barely play the game
And I'm officially the second best smash player in the world. It's a long story. Four minutes and 20 seconds
Okay, it's not that long. I've always wanted to be a Smash Bros. Melee Pro
There is no World Championship. This means I can
create it
My opponent is a CPU Pichu main
Pichu bot is officially the best player in the world. With a new smash game out, now is my chance to take the title.
I guess I just challenged the Pichu bot and beat him. Video over.
I'm going back to main Captain Falcon because if this was an anime, he looks like the main average high school student
Okay, I've been waiting for 10 minutes and he hasn't shown up
Is it because he believes I'm too weak for him? Who does he think he is?
Doesn't he know I've almost figured out how to beat the first boss? Fine. I'll get better at the game first
I need someone to train me. Everyone is posting power tier lists.
No one is posting coaching tier lists.
Top tier: Isabelle
If you want someone ruthless, whiplash style and Ridley, if you want someone who believes in you
Huh? There's an even higher tier
Dragon tier Z: Yoshi
But he refuses to train anyone. Okay, but I'm still gonna pay him a visit because of plot reasons
That's supposed to be the highest tier trainer. Ha, I'm gonna attack him without thinking
Wow getting my ass handed to me has made me realize my own weakness. Now I want to become your apprentice
*Yoshi*
You will accept me I answer an ancient question? Okay, give it to me
What?
Killian couldn't believe its new master
What will you fight your answer to this outrageous question? Find out next time on Smash Bros. U
What? No, I have no idea how to hide the money in the Cayman Islands
*Yoshi*
How can tax evasion be the most important thing to get good at smash?
Oh.
That makes a... perverted kind of sense.
Killian spent three years training with Yoshi to prepare for the Pichu bot
Always cheating on his taxes and using weighted controllers
So how would I...
I don't have a brick
(Tapes a bottle of Pepsi to controller)
Weighted controller.
When he had gone through the training he challenged the top three smash professionals and took out all of them at the same time
But he lost that footage and don't ask them because they will be embarrassed and lie about it
It might seem that he was still bad at the game
That's because he's playing so fast that the untrained eye can't see all the cool stuff he's doing.
The final days went by. It was time to face his enemy.
Game day. I'm nervous
But I've had a big breakfast and-
*huuh*
He's here
the embodiment of evil has arrived
Will they fight or will the switch run out of battery? Find out. Now. They would fight
Game 1: I get to pick a map
Let's smash ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
this is
very easy
uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh
I just spent years, training to beat the level 2 Pichu bot
I just have to use 3 Falcon punches to win
Falcon punch!
This feels.... meaningless, but still I'll be considered the best smash player in the world. So whatever
Falco--
*Megalovania starts playing*
He just stopped the Falcon mid-punch
Oh no
What's happening? What Killian did not know is that this was no ordinary Pichu
When he was very young his entire family was killed by an unnamed villain from an upcoming arc
The young rabbit was rescued by a coach called too radical for smash
He trained Pichu to become the strongest he could be, and also evil for some reason now. Now he's so powerful. I can't beat him
I have to, actually I should just leave. There's no real stakes. I'll just remain number 2
*Yosh Yosh*
Yoshi Sensei. What are you doing here Yoshi-sama No!!
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!!!
Haaaaaaaaaa!!!
Because I was angry for a couple of seconds, I am no longer just any old regular Captain Falcon
I am the guardian of the smash-verse. The protector of future DLC characters
I am the legendary Major Falcon
*Pichu*
You are being defeated Pichu bot. You should give up because my heart is pure and I'm a Gary Stu
What? You're only using 0.2 or two and a half percent of your power
*Piiiichuuuuu*
I can feel that immeasurable power emanating from the switch. His final form might be way more powerful than the legendary Major Falcon
He's so fast there are several of him at the same time
Yet he still has time to put on new hats
You were way more powerful than me, but I can't give up because I fight for my friends
*Pika Pika*
Your final form isn't your final form? you have an even finaler form?
*Pikaaachuuuuu*
He's gonna turn into a Raichu
Or a Pikachu Luchador. He's too powerful, and the planet will explode in ten seconds.
Master Yoshi, I'm sorry I let you down.
*Yoshi*
I still don't understand how to become a great fighter
*Whoa*
What do you mean realise taxation is unconstitutional? What Constitution? You're a cartoon dinosaur
*Huh*
Oh my Smith. All of them.
Is this the power of ultimate tax evader?
Pichu your reign of terror ends now
FALCONNNNN PUUUUNNNNNCHHH!!!
I am now number one. Wait a minute.
Oh
So that's how you triple jump.
Hi there, I just want to tell everyone that the next video is gonna be the first garbage travel guide
Where is a suprise (it's London)